<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Free style writings</title>
    <description>Here I post some of my feelings, ideas or fiction 
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 13:46:38 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 13:46:38 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A wandering cat</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You probably have heard of wandering cats, sometimes they go outside and return beaten up and desperate. Little did Shy knew that he could become a wandering cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mon is his soul other, and they have been away for some time, that’s why they were cherishing the moment on which they could be together, forever. In the past there were days were Shy and Mon would run together through the streets of a great and big city and then sit down by the shored of the big pacific ocean. They were happy walking, painting and playing together. Shy had to go far away, he promised Mon a house were they could be happy togeter, and take care of each other. This was their dream house, because they would be in it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/two-cats.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The days passed and Shy and Mon would always make sure to look at the Moon and communicate. They never missed a single day of communication because the Moon reflected their love and their feelings, it was good enough until Mon could go home with Shy. One day, Shy stepped outside home, there was a cold storm that catched on him, this was not a normal storm, it was a mental storm infused with confusion that made him walk without direction for many days. Because, Shy instead of returning home, wandered alone in a path of cold regret, pain and shame. Every step that Shy made, drove him further away from home. One day, he looked back, and there was just a fuzzy image of the house on the horizon. Shy realized that he was lost, that the storm was driving him away to more agony.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He started his way back home, every step back was gelid, Shy fear that the house would be closed due to the storm, but he kept walking, he only got hope that he could at least get one chance to enter again and eventually see Mon with him one day, in their home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When Shy was thinking on Mon, his heart would start pounding because she was always for him, he knew that Mon would make the house the best place he could wish and now he was scared of not seeing her again. On the storm, every thougth was hard to keep from the fear of dying without Mon and being lost forever, every breath was a gelid reminder of being a wandering cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One day, Shy found his house, the storm tore down many windows and inside was destroyed, Shy cried for eveything he had caused to the house he wanted to share with Mon. He entered the house, and immediatly he knew that Mon was worth it starting the house again. Shy picked up a little hammer and started fixing the windows. He will not stop until the house is once again ready for Mon.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/02/04/wanderingcat/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/02/04/wanderingcat/</guid>
        
        <category>Squid</category>
        
        <category>Mixtape</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Poems of desperation and regret</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;They say my gaze is lost, my aim twisted and in silence I wander.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh, if they knew&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prideful solitude plucked my eyes, and no one shall know,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prideful solitude plucked my eyes, but I will walk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of the horizon, I don’t know, but I want to go back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m losing my heart, and yet I can’t stop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen the end of my journey, only on slippery dreams,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen the end of my journey, on revived memories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I stop … and this is not yet home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel I was born in confusion and fear,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where jail was my room, and honor was exctint.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wished to cry and break my bones, but I’m not even worthy of that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Silence is my confident and my destruction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will I die alone? Surely I don’t want that&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-23.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mistakes have brought my jail, silence please give me light&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I clasp your hand hard, I am far away but life has prepared unavoidable ropes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love, I know I carry a sin, and I know I deserve it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish I know the future, where I’ve been rescued from my past&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fateful steps are agonizing, silence fills my soul&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need air and I am disappearing even when I scream, silence will extinguish my voice&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to survive, I need you back&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2022 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022/02/04/flannel-distillery-asymmetrical/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022/02/04/flannel-distillery-asymmetrical/</guid>
        
        <category>Dummy Text</category>
        
        <category>Moon Drinking</category>
        
        <category>Kale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I am just otter user</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am the husband of a wonderful cat-lover, I want to let her know how wonderful she is and sometimes I don’t have words for it. I will let my keystrokes be better than me to always give her what is deserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like poetry but I must admit I have no experience, in consequence, I do free style poems that I hope have more impact on their meaning than in the play of the English words and intontations. I also like to create little stories about everyday events, because there is complexity in every single episode of life. I must say, I am a bit fanatic of Chaos and Desperation, probably because sometimes I fail to life and fall into them and other times because I know there is order in Chaos and there are solutions for a lot of things in life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/10/23/polaroid-williamsburg/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/10/23/polaroid-williamsburg/</guid>
        
        <category>Dummy Text</category>
        
        <category>Moon Drinking</category>
        
        <category>Kale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
